Good morning. We're from RAW, India.
I'm Mohan Sachdev.
Saurabh Prakash.
Follow me, please.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
What is he doing, sir?
Mr. Maanav.
I'm Mohan Sachdev.
He is Saurabh Prakash.
We're from RAW.
Would you like something?
A statement.
Spiced with the truth.
Tell us from the beginning.
11th September 2022,
I was driving my car,
and Vicky was following me.
We're not interested in Vicky.
How did you manage to reach Katkar?
To reach Katkar,
we'll have to go via Vicky.
You wanted it spiced with truth,
so it might be a little bitter.
-Maanav! Maanav!
Yeah?
Maanav sir,
why did you reject such a big film?
-No. No questions or answers, please.
-That's alright.
Yeah.
It was a gangster biopic.
Being a youth icon,
I have a certain social responsibility.
The underworld and thugs,
they're not relevant anymore.
If there's no relevance,
why lodge a police complaint
and waste government resources?
Because I'm an action hero.
I reserve my strength for the end.
-Maanav! Maanav!
Maanav!
Saeed, Maanav will go directly
to the showroom after the shoot.
Keep the paperwork and the car ready.
He's waited for three months now.
He has driven me crazy!
No last-minute problems, please.
See you. Bye.
Maanav.
Come on!
The shot is ready, the crew is waiting
and you haven't started
your workout yet!
Bro, you're not going
on the set without working out, okay?
You act so cute sometimes.
Look at your competitors around you.
They all have it, they're flaunting it
and capitalizing on it, while you--
Enough of your rules and regulations!
You've worked so hard to build an image.
We have.
You're an action hero,
you have to look like one.
Always ready to fight goons anytime.
I don't need to fight boys.
I need to avenge my brother's death.
No one will look at these abs.
The audience wants
to see the fury in my eyes.
People get their money's worth only
when they see an action hero angry.
So you're not able to get angry?
I get it,
and so will the director.
But the audience outside,
they won't understand!
Let's go.
-Maanav!
-Hi!
I am Tillu.
Sir, I'm a journalist.
-Maanav! Maanav!
Maanav!
Ready, Maanav?
Roll sound.
Roll camera.
And action!
-Cut it!
-Cut!
-Sorry, guys.
-Maanav.
Hello, Mr. Producer!
What's up?
Climax.
Avenging my brother's death.
I'm not able to feel the anger.
Now that you're here, I'm sure I will.
Come on, sir.
-Sir, Vicky Solanki is here.
-Who is he?
Bhoora Solanki,
the local Municipal Councilor,
who's permitted us to shoot here.
Vicky is his younger brother.
He is contesting the elections
and wants to take a photo with you.
We'll also get some publicity.
It'll only take five minutes, sir.
I give ten hours.
Everyday.
Don't belittle it.
I don't want to be disturbed.
We're all working here.
Not fooling around!
Call for you, Maanav.
Scoot.
Please don't read my messages.
He is not able to get angry.
Make him!
Make him angry!
It's the climax!
Make him angry, Roshan.
-Ma'am, can you please sort the costumes?
-Yeah, I'm on it.
It's okay, calm down.
Yes, madam?
Yes, sir?
When will your hero be free?
Give us two minutes.
Two minutes have turned into two hours!
I understand, sir.
I'll have a word with him.
Please, give me two minutes.
Listen.
You're free, right?
Why don't you give me two minutes?
Something is missing here, Maanav.
-I know what's missing.
-What?
-This--
-Maanav sir.
Sir, Vicky needs to leave for some work,
if you could spare two minutes.
Just look at the screen.
Something is missing here.
You know what?
My anger.
I've been trying all morning
but I'm not able to feel it.
When I do get angry, it'll be bad.
Don't be a reason for that.
Explain it to her.
Maanav, just a second.
Sir, your coffee.
Should I drag him here?
Drink your beer.
Saeed had called--
Is the car ready?
Book the circuit tonight.
After this take, we're going for a spin.
Actually, the paperwork isn't ready yet.
He called to say this, Maanav.
I've waited for three months now.
Wait another week.
Is this a joke?
You should've told me,
you can't arrange it.
I'd have asked someone else.
It's not that easy.
It's not difficult either.
I paid in advance.
What more does he want?
He'd promised to deliver it tonight.
Where is my car?
Call up Saeed.
-But--
-Call him right now, I said.
The car will be delivered
after a week, I'm sorry.
Thanks, Roshan.
I'm ready.
Okay, let's go, guys.
Let's do this.
Roll sound.
Roll camera.
And action!
Cut!
Superb!
Nice one, sir!
Sir, tea?
Tea?
Go and tell your big boss,
I'm keeping count.
-Okay, sir.
-Got it?
Go on.
Yes, sir is on his way.
Sir.
Someone is waiting for you.
Oh man, Guddu.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
The film shoot is over.
To hell with it!
I've been saying, let's barge in.
But this guy refuses to do so.
Elections are around the corner.
One wrong step
and Bhoora will whip my ass!
Tell you what,
say that you'll handle Bhoora.
And then I'll show them what shooting is!
Will you?
Will you handle him?
The hero is here.
Maanav, come with me.
Come.
-What about the photo?
-An autograph!
Sir, please. Over here.
You said you weren't getting angry so…
Bastard!
What the…
Give me the keys.
Should I come along?
Turn the car around!
Who are you?
I'm Vicky Solanki.
Bhoora's brother.
Turn it around.
You made us wait for
hours and then drove off.
You think I'm a fool?
Bro, I was going to meet you when
Guddu told me, the car had arrived.
I'll set Guddu and the car, both on fire!
Turn it around.
Wait a minute.
Do one thing, come to my hotel tomorrow,
and bring your brother along as well.
We'll have breakfast together
and you can take a photo as well.
What do you think?
Turn the car around right now!
Watch your tone!
Or what?
Let go of my collar.
Let go of my collar!
I won't.
Then I won't go either!
Go tell your brother,
I don't care.
-You--
-Get lost!
Get up, bro.
Hello.
What's your name?
Vicky.
Are you okay?
Listen to what my heart says
Here you go, sir.
For once, add some water or ice maybe?
If we were meant to add water,
they would've been selling it
with water added already!
It works best without.
Drink up, sir.
Haryana is the best place to drink!
Open skies, cool breeze,
a white Fortuner,
a dead body on the roadside.
Stop the car.
Reverse.
Stop.
What's really inside dumplings?
My moon--
Policemen get into a fight…
Fearless superstar Maanav took
on the underworld and said…
It was a gangster biopic.
Being a youth icon,
I have a certain social responsibility.
The underworld and thugs,
they're not relevant anymore.
Is he a real-life action hero?
He is bleeding, sir.
His phone is also ringing.
-Call for an ambulance.
-Yes, sir.
Check if he's breathing.
Check who is calling.
Who is it?
Oh, my God!
Hello.
Where are you?
Jai Hind, sir.
Hello?
This is Roopkumar,
the officer-in-charge
the of Mandothi Police Station.
Yes, tell me.
Wanted to speak to you about Vicky.
Okay, give him phone.
Vicky is dead.
His body was found near the bridge.
Roti, sir?
You're watching Mandothi Express.
A dead body was found in Mandothi.
Tillu Mandothiya is reporting
from the spot.
Mr. Tillu, over to you.
We've just received news that
Vicky Solanki's body was found
near a bridge at Mandothi village.
Bhoora Solanki, Vicky's elder brother,
has reached the crime scene.
According to the officer-in-charge
Mr. Roopkumar,
apart from the Fortuner,
there was a black car at the site,
the side mirror of which,
was found on the road.
Bhoora's men have snatched away
the side mirror for their investigation.
According to sources, whoever is
behind this, Bhoora is after them.
With cameraman Chandalal, this is Tillu.
Goodbye.
Get lost!
Let's go
Look where life has brought me
I'm overwhelmed
And I have to face the truth
I'm in trouble as fate is not on my side
Things haven't gone as per my plan
This star has been dimmed by darkness
The storm is my only refuge now
Get away now
Get back up and never stay down
See the light at the end of the tunnel
You gotta run, you gotta run run run
Get ready to rumble
Run away as fast as you can
The action in your life starts now
From where do I even begin?
Let me bring light to this shiny world
Life can turn topsy-turvy anytime
A hero can become a villain in a flash
A romantic scene can turn into a thriller
And a lover boy can become a killer
Roshan, arrange for a flight to Mumbai.
A charter flight. Now.
Now? What happened?
Just do as I say!
Okay.
You ain't got the time to think
Shut your mind, trust your instincts
In a wave of thoughts, don't let that sink
Cause know your life
Can change in one blink
And right or wrong
Don't wait too long
Pick up yourself and move on
Get away now
Get back up and never stay down
See the light at the end of the tunnel
You gotta run, you gotta run run run
Get ready to rumble
-Don't ever look back
-Do that
-Stay on your track
-And move
-You gotta move fast
-Fast
The past is past, at last
Come on, come on! Leave!
MANDOTHI POLICE STATION
Where's your office in-charge?
-So…
-We've been standing here forever!
Why are you behaving like a thug?
Why have you grown such a long beard?
Sir, I don't know anything.
About what?
I don't know anything
about anything, sir.
Why are you here then?
I'm the DOP, sir.
It's called DCP, you idiot!
DOP means nothing!
It does! Director of Photography, sir.
You can call yourself anything.
This is my work, sir.
What work do you do for society?
Do you grow vegetables?
Do you heal people?
Do you protect people?
How is your work relevant to society?
Now you've built
an industry around this work!
Your industry is full of druggies,
terrorists, and murderers.
-You are… a bloody Naxalite!
-No, sir.
-Only they grow such beards!
Sir…
the reporters are here.
Excuse me. Can I get one selfie?
-Hello!
-Mannu…
how are you, my action hero?
Bad scene, sir.
How bad?
Film it again.
We're actors, we should keep trying
till we perfect the scene.
You'll win the Oscar for India someday.
Why are you pulling my leg, sir?
We're just two people making small talk.
We could be two people keeping quiet!
Fine, I'll keep quiet. So rude!
Sorry, sir.
Hear me out.
-The officer is here.
-He's here.
He's here.
Officer, how did all this happen?
One person at a time.
Sir, is it true that it's
Vicky Solanki's body?
The body has been sent
for further examination.
We will inform you about the report.
I've heard,
you're questioning the film crew.
We asked them some routine questions.
We're conducting an inquiry.
We will let you know.
Sir, do you suspect anyone?
If I tell you, he'll run away.
He already has!
I tried to stop him.
I said, "Don't run,
the police are conducting an inquiry."
He said, "It will take a long time then."
Start your inquiry, officer.
As far as I know, just before he died,
Vicky had gone to meet movie star Maanav.
The side mirror of
a black Mustang was found at the site.
This car was delivered
to the film set last night.
What do you have to say about this?
Good.
I'm really proud of the media.
We're conducting our inquiry,
you look into the matter as well.
As we find out more details
we can exchange information
and our country will see more progress.
Jai Hind!
-As you saw, the officer
-Bring him in.
-was with us--
-Excuse me, sir!
-Sir, give us answers!
-Let me go, sir.
Where are you taking me? Guys, help!
I've worked very hard to build my career.
Toiled day and night.
I will lose everything.
You've experienced everything.
Please, suggest something.
Speaking from experience,
may I tell you something?
Yes please, sir?
Don't tell anyone that we met.
Please.
Tell me.
Who told you all this?
Secret sources.
What exactly did your
secret sources tell you?
They said you need to pay up.
Done.
How?
I'm the officer-in-charge here, idiot.
And what can an officer-in-charge do?
I'll roll the banknotes
and shove it up your ass.
You wouldn't need to go to an ATM.
Feel free to reach in
for cash whenever you want.
-Want an advance payment?
-No, it's okay!
Officer,
Maanav is the prime suspect in this case.
Suraj Bhan has gone to arrest him.
He has already fled.
Where to?
He has taken a charter,
let's find out where it lands.
I won't surrender, sir.
Why should I?
I'm innocent.
But you're the one who pushed him.
Maybe you should go
to prison for some time.
It's an unintentional murder.
You'll be sentenced to two years.
At least it won't be for 14 years!
You might even find a good story there.
I didn't go to Haryana
to commit an unintentional murder.
I had gone there for work.
I hadn't even called anyone to the shoot.
What is your plan now?
Sorry.
The same as Mallya and Nirav.
I'll ask my lawyer to prepare a case.
I'll fight it from here.
While sitting in London?
Yes.
I won't return.
I think you're capable.
You're a brave guy.
Good luck, brother.
Sir, can you please do me a favor?
What?
The paparazzi are waiting outside.
If you could go first,
chat with them.
I'll drop in later.
How do I look?
Sir, I love your action films.
A selfie?
He's better. Take one with him.
-Mr. Anupam, one question, please.
-Sir.
Are you dating Shalini?
You guys get to know everything.
-Come, let's chat.
-Sure.
Namaskar, I'm Sanjana Sharma.
You're watching India's number one
news channel, News 24x7.
It's 6:00 p.m. right now.
We'll start with news of a murder.
The prime suspect in the Haryana murder
that happened last night,
is Superstar Maanav.
Look into the camera.
You can smile.
Where is Superstar Maanav?
-Welcome home.
-Thank you.
Sources say Vicky Solanki had gone
to meet Maanav on a film set.
Mr. Maanav?
Please, come with us.
It's reported, that last night,
at Maanav's film set,
a black Mustang was delivered to him.
A side-view mirror was
found at the accident site.
The dark and rotting underbelly
of Bollywood is falling apart.
Ashamed to say this,
but this is the dark truth of Bollywood!
Will Maanav surrender?
Or will he be arrested?
Hi, I'm Vishwas Patel.
Your attorney.
Roshan spoke to me last night.
Oh, man!
I want to ask you some questions
to prepare the case.
Sure.
Why are you here?
I have a house here.
I've been thinking of coming here and
someone died at my hands last night.
I thought this is the right time
for me to come to the UK.
The Judge will ask you
this question, not me.
Thanks, man.
Tell the judge,
Guddu was driving the car…
and he caused the accident.
Roshan has spoken to Guddu.
Guddu has agreed.
Anyway,
I'll file the papers tomorrow,
till then you think about it.
And please,
stay inside your house.
Want me to drop you home?
Maanav?
Yeah, no.
I'll manage.
-Sure?
-Thank you.
Don't switch on your phone.
I'll see you.
One more.
To dispel the aura of death,
take this holy fire around the house.
Where is Maanav?
He has gone to London.
What's wrong, sir?
He came to Haryana from Bombay,
killed Vicky, and left.
What were you guys doing?
Conducting an inquiry.
And what did you find out?
That he's in London.
We will nab him, sir.
Even if he goes to the moon,
I'll tie him to my car,
drag him here, and throw him at your feet.
You'll be amazed to see me do that.
Do you want to drive this car to the moon?
And drag him back here?
Right?
Will you go alone?
Or they'll go as well?
They'll go with me.
Take off your clothes.
-Clothes?
-Take off your clothes!
The moon? You don't deserve
to go around the neighborhood!
I have packed your bag.
Brother.
Here's his London address.
I would've found it on the internet.
Why didn't you go with him?
I'd asked him, brother.
But he didn't reply.
Did you ask him again?
So tell me, why didn't you go with him?
The actor was also alone.
All of you are fake!
Cremate him, Father.
At least stay till
the rituals are complete.
I want to get to him before the police do.
These three stay naked till I return.
Okay, brother.
Excuse me, sir.
Would you let the child sit
on the window seat?
He wants to look outside.
Should I put him on the wings,
for a better view?
Hello?
How are you, Guddu?
Sir?
I am well, sir.
Don't worry.
Roshan said,
negligence of driving has
a jail term of only six months.
I'll manage, sir.
You know it wasn't my fault, right?
I know that, sir. Please don't worry.
I know, it isn't your fault either.
So neither you nor will I take the blame.
Look, I'm not over there,
so no matter what the lawyer,
Roshan, or police tell you,
you'll only tell them the truth.
Get it?
Okay, sir.
Sir, I'm just…
a little scared.
You need not be scared.
I'm with you.
Everyone is out to make a quick buck.
I have enough to pay them all off!
Get it?
Will you do me a favor?
Sure, sir.
They've taken my car
to the police station.
Ask someone to put a cover on it.
Else everyone will have a go at it.
Sir, the car was being taken
to the police station when
the villagers set it on fire.
Hello?
Sir?
I really don't feel like having a panel
of intellectuals to discuss so.
I don't feel like sharing
my personal opinions.
Because for the first time,
the first time
in my entire career of 20 years,
the question is very simple
and straightforward.
Our action hero,
our youth icon of 2019.
Where are you?
Tell us where are you hiding?
Bloody fakes!
The whole lot of them!
Hi, there are cops outside my house.
An FIR has been registered in India.
They must have been informed.
It's a routine check. Don't worry.
-Hello?
-All my stuff is inside the house.
Passport, ID, everything.
They can't enter without a warrant.
I'm going to file
the papers in court now.
Stay out of sight.
I'll call you as soon as it's done.
Come to my office then.
Okay.
Hello. We're from the MET Police.
We got a call.
We've just come to see
if everything's alright.
Shots fired! Man down!
Someone fired a gun.
Shots fired inside the house!
Calm down, Maanav.
I don't understand.
What happened?
The cops were inside the house,
someone else was inside.
Two shots were fired.
Who was inside?
The cops!
Okay.
Two shots were fired. Both died.
Hello?
Hello!
I'm sorry but the person you've called
is not available.
Please leave your message after the tone.
-Hey, stop right there!
-Stop!
Where do you think you're going?
-Hey, stop! Get him!
-Hey, stop!
I need backup!
-You! Stop it, right now!
-I need backup!
Stop him!
Hey!
Sir!
-Hey!
-Watch out!
Go on, get up there!
What are you waiting for?
What are you doing?
Get off here!
Keep following him.
Careful! I'm gonna fall!
What are you doing?
Hey! You!
Hey!
No! My car! Come on!
Someone, call the cops!
Give me the keys.
Give me the keys!
Recognize me?
Look at me carefully.
I left home yesterday.
I haven't even taken off my shoes!
I've killed two men since morning.
I must be someone!
Bhoora Solanki,
Municipal Councillor of Mandothi, Haryana.
Have you been there?
For what?
Film shooting.
How did Vicky die?
It was an accident.
I tried to move him away and…
he fell and died.
He'd eat four big meals a day,
four glasses of milk,
and built like an ox!
You're trying to tell me
you moved him away
and he fell and died?
Are you really that strong?
An action hero?
I want to fight you.
-But why?
-I want to kill you.
With my own hands.
I want to rip you apart!
Come.
I swear, I won't use this.
Come on.
-I'm telling you the truth--
-Fight me!
Action hero my foot!
Come on.
Look here--
Listen to me,
I don't want to fight.
You have to!
Listen to me, Solanki.
I'll fight to stay alive,
not to take revenge.
I don't have time to argue with you.
Stand up.
Why are you glaring?
You've flown down from India.
If you die without killing me,
villagers will shame you and your family!
Come on.
Stand up.
Walk.
Hurry up.
This way.
Open the trunk.
Get in.
Get in!
I fight because it's my job,
I don't do it for fun.
-Hello?
-Hi Roshan, Maanav here.
Where are you, Maanav?
What's going on?
Why isn't Patel answering my calls?
Wow! What a coincidence!
I'm calling to ask you the same thing.
Where are you? What's going on?
Why isn't Patel answering my calls?
Is this what I've kept you guys for?
Maanav, please, relax.
What do you mean relax?
There's a man inside the trunk
of this car I'm leaning against!
-But why?
-Because if I let him out,
he'll kill me!
-What!
-Yes!
I've been paying you for ten years.
Make yourself useful!
I'm on the A1 Motorway.
Do something right now!
-I'll figure something out.
-Now, Roshan!
I will!
I'm telling you the truth.
I didn't kill Vicky.
Bhoora?
Don't tell me, you're dead too!
Hello.
-Maanav?
-Who is this?
Roshan called me.
Yes, tell me.
-Blacksmiths at 10:00 p.m.
-What?
Blacksmiths at 10:00 p.m.
-Blacksmiths, 10:00 p.m. Sure.
-Yeah.
Blacksmiths, 10:00 p.m.
Blacksmiths.
Return to India if you manage to get out.
I'll do the same.
The prime suspect in
the Vicky Solanki murder case,
Maanav, is missing.
He can't be found!
He won't be found!
A murderer can't be found easily.
One has to search for him.
Ding-dong goes the bell in my head
I see colors in the wind
Like dropping a stone in still waters
That sends ripples all around
While it's evening here
It's morning elsewhere
Everything is a circle in this world
As I lift my head
I see the excitement all around
As fast-paced as my heartbeat
There was a shootout
at Maanav's UK residence.
And according to reports,
two policemen were found dead.
He shouldn't have run away.
Come back after a short break.
The show is called Maanav the Monster.
Trapped
My mind feels so trapped
Circus! Simply, a circus.
He shouldn't have run away.
The stars might have fallen from the sky
But the fireflies have brought light
Those sunny days have gone by
Now there's darkness everywhere
Sources have revealed
that all assets belonging to
the superstar Maanav, have been frozen
with immediate effect
until further notice.
I've lost my way
Don't know where I'm headed
I'm going in circles
Time is not in my favor
Luck is not on my side
My fate has let me down…
Where are you?
Where are you hiding?
I don't know where I am, Roshan.
We want to know!
Nation wants to know!
Trapped
My mind feels so trapped
Can I help you, sir?
Eight houses, 11 cars, and two passports.
Why is the nation's sweetheart
running away from the police?
Do you know where Blacksmith Arms is?
Straight. It's just that way.
Thanks, man.
I really don't understand
why do they all flee to the UK?
What's so special about the UK?
Fear is my companion
Now that things have changed
I'm struggling to breathe
Death follows me
Poison is my only cure
My heart battles itself
Excuse me.
Do you need help?
Yes, please.
Would you mind? Thank you!
Trapped
My mind feels so trapped
Give me drugs!
Trapped
Mate, you've fucking pissed your pants!
Look at that. Look!
You've actually gone and wet yourself.
Mate, you okay?
Is this what Roshan arranged?
A dosa?
Tell me how you like it.
-It's good.
-Good, right?
Roshan told me to feed you first.
Tell me, what now?
This morning at my house…
I want the footage.
This morning's footage
of the front lawn.
Of the shootout?
You're on every television channel today.
You'll get it.
Thirty thousand.
Fifty thousand.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Your address?
The CCTV is not on.
I'm visiting after two years.
Even if it was,
I wouldn't access it.
Why?
The punishment for that is seven years.
We'll check the license plates
of cars near the house
and get their dashcam footage.
The Motor Vehicle Act can
send me to prison for six months.
Got it?
Are you a lawyer?
Yes. Till 5:00 p.m.
After that?
Chef.
And after 10:00 p.m.?
Extra-curricular activities.
Can you give me your address, please?
36, Silver Oaks.
Yes!
Done?
The computation is on.
The Motor Department site has a password.
The probability ratio
is one in 1.35 million.
It'll take some time.
How long?
Five hours, maximum.
It will be done.
Take this number.
His name is Li Xian.
He'll give you the footage.
So what do you do?
Dude, I break the code.
I'm the cool guy.
Checking the footage after getting access,
finding the right piece,
and delivering it,
is labor work.
The Chinese are good at it.
Can I stay here till it's done?
Not here. At my house, you can.
Where is your house?
The place from where you started walking.
What will you do with this footage?
I'll give it to the police,
tell them I haven't killed those two cops.
The UK police could've done
this by themselves.
They'd need proof to send you to prison.
The police don't have the footage.
How do you know?
If they did,
they'd be looking for that Bhoore.
Who is Bhoore?
The one who killed the cops.
-Was he in London?
-No.
I think he got here this morning.
He must've started last night.
No, in the morning.
When did you get here?
Last night.
So you started the night before?
Actually, it was morning here in London.
Bhoora started in the morning.
Did you guys arrive together?
Are you fucking stupid?
It's a ten-hour flight and
a five-and-a-half-hour time difference.
Days are shorter than nights.
It rains at any bloody time of the day.
Focus on driving, fucker!
Stop the car!
What is it?
I had locked Bhoora
inside the trunk of this car.
So this guy Bhoore…
-Bhoora.
-Yeah, whatever.
What does he want from you?
He wants to kill me.
But that's not allowed.
What do you mean?
When two Indians meet
in a foreign country,
they only sing praises of India.
Don't you watch Hindi films?
What did I just tell you?
-I'm paying you.
-More than I asked for.
I'll pay you even more!
Please leave me alone for ten minutes.
Alright.
Yes, Sai.
I've cooked your favorite dish.
It's called "superstar on a plate."
Want it?
Maanav?
Yes.
Where?
In my kitchen.
How much?
Art is expensive.
This one is going to cost you.
Fine. I'll be right there.
Okay.
I told you to leave.
Why are you back?
I was missing you.
Come on, we met this morning!
Forgot already?
We spent all morning getting
to know each other.
I was thinking maybe two Indians
could sit and chitchat about our lives.
What do you say?
That's what we see in films.
This is real life, not a film.
One bullet can end it all!
Go back.
Okay.
Won't you let me leave now?
You have a strange way of expressing love.
Yes, my love is also known
as a 9mm Glock.
Nice.
In that case,
your love has only two bullets left.
What do you want, man?
To fight you. I told you.
Here I come.
One.
Why get into a gunfight?
History is witness,
that only wars decide,
who's right and who's wrong.
Where did you go?
One bullet left.
But no more patience left.
Come.
Let's clear this up once and for all.
Don't you get it?
I didn't kill Vicky!
I won't get it!
Because he died at your hands.
People make mistakes, Bhoora.
People worship actors like you!
And you say you made a mistake?
Age-old tradition says,
youngsters make mistakes
but the elders set an example!
Today I'll make an example out of you!
People aren't stupid
to set things aside
and go watch your films.
The thing you call your livelihood
is only due to the love we shower on you!
If we tell you to dance, you dance.
If we tell you to sing, you sing.
And if we want a photo, you will oblige!
We have made you the stars,
you will do as we say!
I thought you were here
to avenge your brother's death.
But it seems to me,
that I've hurt your ego!
What do you mean?
I mean, enough of your
"I'll kill you" nonsense.
Pick up that gun and kill me.
Kill me.
Come on.
Up.
Up!
-Maanav?
-Yes.
Go sit in the car.
Who are you?
-Kaadir.
-Kaadir who?
Don't you recognize anyone?
Are we all bloody crazy,
to want to kill you?
Who is he?
Vicky's brother.
-Vicky who?
-My brother.
Who are you, mister?
Kaadir.
-Get him into the car.
-No!
If you act too smart, I'll act stupid!
Get it?
Take his gun, Maanav.
Okay.
Let's go.
Enough of the chitchat, Mr. Kaadir.
-Let's go out.
-Put your guns down.
Go out.
Good job.
Hands up.
Step away.
If you had any idea of who I am,
you wouldn't dare to hold me by my collar.
But I have.
I'm holding you by the neck as well!
Any smart move and I'll shoot you.
Everybody, guns down.
Don't be stupid, Maanav. Come with us.
Am I fucking stupid
to have come all this way?
He is coming with me.
Maanav, open the car door.
Don't worry about this guy.
We'll take care of him.
I promised Sai, you wouldn't be harmed.
Sai is dead. So is your promise.
Open the car door.
I'll take care of these guys. Come on.
Don't do this, Maanav. Let's go.
Let's go.
Sit in the back.
-Maanav.
-Shut up.
Sit inside.
Go get him!
Waiting for me to say it in Urdu?
Follow him!
I want him alive.
Don't kill him.
Will they catch him?
Of course.
And where will they take him?
He is going towards the city.
Maanav, Roshan here.
Roshan, I'll handle things from here.
You're fired.
What do you mean by "you're fired"?
Did you meet Sai?
-I did. He is dead.
-How?
Because of acute pressure on the windpipe.
What the hell are you saying?
He was killed.
-By whom?
-By Bhoora.
Who is Bhoora?
The guy I locked inside the car trunk.
He has come all
the way from India to kill me.
Why did he kill Sai?
Good that he did.
The rascal betrayed me!
-To whom?
-To Kaadir.
Who is Kaadir?
I have no idea, Roshan!
I have no idea.
I don't know any of them.
Till yesterday, everyone I met
wanted a photo with me,
and now, everyone wants to kill me!
I didn't know anyone then
and I don't know anyone now!
But everyone knows who you are, bro.
Things have changed here.
I called all my contacts but
none of them answered my call.
No one will help, Roshan.
Nor can you.
What do you mean?
This is my battle.
I'll have to fight it, alone.
Listen to me,
you're an action hero.
You can pretend to fight,
not fight for real.
Things have changed, Roshan.
I've learned to fight.
You ain't got the time to think
Get away now
Get back up and never stay down
Are you from India?
Is this your first visit to the UK?
What do you want from Maanav?
I want to take a photo with him.
A person travels so far only
for two things,
love… or revenge.
Not just for a photo, man.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome to this wonderful
tour of the London boat.
My name is Greg and I'm your guide.
Please settle down.
We'll be beginning with our tour shortly.
As you can see we're on the river Thames.
-Oh, yeah.
-And you'll be able to see
-Do you want to go say hi?
-all the attractions on this tour.
-It's going to be…
-Can I get your autograph?
Maanav hasn't just murdered a farmer,
he has murdered his audience's trust!
It's a clear case
of serial killing, viewers.
And I have proof tonight.
Haryana Youth Committee has declared
a ban on Maanav's films
in Delhi and the NCR area.
Maanav, who we thought
was as brave as a lion,
turned out to be a hyena!
He has signed seven films.
The industry has invested over
1000 crores in his films.
And you want us to boycott him?
Yes.
Apart from the lead actor,
there are many people
who work on a film.
If films don't get made,
how will they earn a living?
The underworld and thugs,
they're not relevant anymore.
The man who had challenged
the underworld joins them!
I'm an action hero.
I reserve my strength for the end.
It's time we changed our heroes!
People are protesting on the streets.
Things are getting ugly.
-Down with Maanav!
You drug addict, substance abuser,
hiding like a coward.
Where are you hiding?
Nation wants to know!
#JusticeforVicky
The rascal should be shot!
These addicts drive when they are high.
They don't care
if they run over animals or people.
#JusticeforVicky
Hi, I'm at Trafalgar.
You better have that footage, Li Xian.
I'm on my way.
Under pressure, the police commissioner
has given him 24 hours.
The Epic Fall of Superstar Maanav,
powered by Genda Saria.
Viewers, please tell us,
what punishment does Maanav deserve?
Total life imprisonment?
Removal from the country?
Or to be punished by hanging?
If your answer is total life imprisonment,
type "T."
If your answer is removal
from the country, type "R."
If your answer is punishment by hanging,
type "P."
Type "TRP"
if the answer is all of the above.
Suspect identified outside the premises.
Need immediate backup now.
Hey!
Who are you guys?
You kidnapped me
right in front of a police station!
Is this a movie?
Come on.
Yes, sir.
Where is Kaadir?
Actually, there was someone else
with Maanav at Sai's house.
Kaadir is with that guy.
And Maanav?
We've picked him up, brother.
He's with us.
Bring him here.
Okay, brother.
God bless.
Who are you guys?
Let me go.
I'll pay you a lot of money. I am rich.
We don't want your money.
What do you want?
Nothing.
Then why did you kidnap me?
Because it's our job.
You work for money don't you, bro?
No. We like our job.
Wow!
I wouldn't have been able
to avenge Vicky's death
without your help, Kaadir.
I will never forget this.
But who is Vicky?
Ask this question…
when you meet him.
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Hi.
I'm Katkar.
Katkar?
Katkar who?
Masood Abraham Katkar.
You?
The guy who was killed
off in D-Day by you guys.
You mean?
You're the same…
don?
-I mean--
-What do you mean?
Wondering where's my mustache?
My cigarette, my Ray-Ban glasses?
All that the media has shown you
for 30 years.
I've cut off my mustache!
Doctors have told me to stop smoking.
And if I wear a Ray-Ban at night,
I'll look fucking stupid!
My voice may not sound the same but
it still carries the same weight.
-Want proof?
-No.
But--
What?
You and me, together?
We are no different
from each other, Mr. Maanav.
Both of us are on the run.
Weren't you in Karachi, sir?
Who told you this?
The media.
The media also says
that you've murdered Vicky Solanki.
The media is a caged dragon,
that breathes fire every time
it opens its mouth.
Tell me, what do you want?
Sir, please ask someone
to drop me off at the
nearest police station.
I want to surrender.
I have proof, I'll set everything right.
That's what you think.
Because you don't know who you are.
Me?
Yes.
I'm Maanav.
Superstar Maanav?
You're an opportunity.
When a rich man is down and out,
he becomes an opportunity for the poor.
The India you're dying to return to
is waiting to seize this opportunity.
As soon as you return,
the truth and the proof
will become useless.
And you won't be able to do a thing.
I have an offer for you.
I will fix everything.
Not the way you think,
where you'll return,
fight a case, start afresh. No.
It'll be my way.
You'll return the same way you came
and no one will know.
Why would you want to help me?
So that you know,
no matter how long it's been,
I still am relevant!
I'm really sorry, sir.
You're probably hurt
by some statement I've made.
Just don't--
Just ignore it.
Sir, may I leave?
Thank you, sir.
Maanav.
You're an action hero, aren't you?
You reserve your strength for the end.
Let's use that strength.
I don't understand.
My granddaughter is getting married.
Dance with all your strength.
-Excuse me?
-You're performing in half an hour.
Dance like there's no tomorrow.
Show me the photo.
Good job.
Circulate it.
Let the world know,
even after all these years
superstars still dance at my parties!
Just like flowers need spring
And spring a garden
Heart needs a heart
And a body needs another
Everyone is seeking a union
I wish you fall in love with me
It'll be amazing
Yes, so amazing
If someone like you comes into my life
It'll be amazing
Yes, so amazing
I don't know what's come over me
I feel intoxicated
And have forgotten the world
As I lose myself in your arms
I am only human, not an angel
I'm scared I'll give in to temptation
My poor heart yearns for your love
Cause there's no one like you
It'll be amazing
Yes, so amazing
If someone like you comes into my life
It'll be amazing
Yes, so amazing
How are you known?
By my name.
He's asking what your name is.
Bhoora.
Are you serious?
Sir, that is his name.
Are you his lawyer?
I've done as you asked.
Please let me go now.
What do you plan to do?
You couldn't even break the glass!
Action hero, my foot!
I needed permission to bring you here.
I lost my men.
I waited on the rooftop.
Did all this hurt your ego?
So, why did you
open fire at the wedding?
That's the custom where I come from.
And I'll stay right till the end but
-first I'll kill this guy--
-Again!
You have killed Vicky--
I have not killed Vicky, mister!
I didn't know him.
I didn't call him.
He followed me himself
and died by himself too!
Just like you've followed me.
And you!
The way things are going,
you two will die too!
I am so done with all this!
I won't do anything now.
I won't run, won't surrender,
won't fight, won't dance.
I will sit here.
I'm sitting on this chair
and I dare you to make me budge!
After 25 years of hard work,
our channel has procured some extremely
super-exclusive pictures of Maanav.
But that's not the only
thing to look at in this
beautifully clicked,
picture-perfect moment.
Look at who is on the left.
Any guesses?
Who is not differentiating between color,
international borders, or race?
Any guesses?
Masood.
Masood Abraham Katkar!
I've never ever seen such a killer
ever in my entire career of 20 years!
Bachelors in Smuggling and Extortion!
And Masters in Arms Dealing
and Bomb Blasts!
The genius, the mastermind would-be!
A three-time nominee for…
You shouldn't keep your
enemy alive for long,
you might become friends.
But in reality, he was just a focused,
meticulously hard-working,
A-grade international terrorist for years.
After 25 years of hard work,
our channel has procured some extremely
super-exclusive pictures of Maanav.
The entire nation is confused
and every soul is searching for the truth.
Only the truth!
There is just one person,
one person who knows it.
The one who has no fear.
The one person you
all are looking for is me.
That's me!
What have you done?
But I didn't do anything.
You killed him.
I didn't…
I was aiming at you
and you pushed my hand.
You mean, you didn't do anything?
And he just died?
You must be really strong!
I want to fight you.
Stop this nonsense.
Let's go back, Bhoora…
and see what happens.
If I return without killing you
the villagers will shame me and my family.
That was just a line.
They really will!
I would've done the same.
Will you kill for such a petty thing?
It is not about that.
It's about keeping my word.
And I am someone who keeps his word!
Who even thinks like that anymore?
I'm sure those three policemen are,
they're waiting for me to return.
Seven lakh people have voted for me.
"Bhoora Singh Solanki is a fighter!"
"We want a leader like Bhoora!"
They'll laugh at me
if I don't finish what I set out to do.
So you must die.
Get it?
Only then will the villagers
honor me with a plaque.
Bhoora Singh Solanki,
son of Suraj Bhan Solanki,
killed his brother's murderer
and the country's biggest enemy, Bhaskar.
Katkar.
Whatever!
They'll put up a plaque,
and the world will respect me.
Know why?
Because all's well that ends well.
You're the audience, aren't you?
Aren't you?
Yes. So?
Behave like the audience.
Don't decide the ending.
I decide the ending.
Why do you get to decide?
Because I'm the action hero.
I became one today!
Not because I've fought off cops or goons
but because I've fought my fate.
The story that's been playing out…
is not yours, Vicky's, or Katkar's,
it is my story…
of how I became an action hero.
Listen.
Let's leave while we're still alive.
I will kill you.
I have a plan.
You mean to say,
you saw his reflection on the screen
and turned the bullet toward Katkar?
Must've been a freak shot, sir.
It can't be otherwise.
I've practiced for years.
Used it in two films as well.
The audience gave me a standing ovation.
Not sure if I should
laugh at your story or…
be annoyed by how childish it is.
It's your loss either way.
Me leaving India, meeting Katkar,
the proof and the footage of the same
will be given to you by the UK police.
But what really happened in that room,
I am the only living witness to that.
I've heard fancier stories.
If there was an iota of truth in it,
I'd believe you
but this story is hard to believe.
Let me tell you why.
For the first time in a story,
the villager is the villain
and the film star is innocent.
It is difficult to believe it,
but it'll be even more difficult for you
when the public asks you
that if I can kill him,
then why the hell couldn't you,
in the last 30 years?
According to sources,
international terrorist
Masood Abraham Katkar has been killed.
The person that is behind all of this is…
Maanav.
We have breaking news coming in.
British Intelligence
has released an exclusive photo of
someone who looks like superstar Maanav
is sitting beside a dead body.
The dead body might be
that of Masood Abraham Katkar!
We aren't saying he is innocent.
But we should let
the judiciary do its duty!
Why are we pressurizing the judiciary
to do its duty?
This is to inform you
of the recent developments
that have occurred
during our operations,
where the most wanted
Masood Abraham Katkar
has been eliminated.
-Sir, one question.
-Sir!
-One by one, please. One by one.
-One question, sir.
-Yes, ma'am?
-Sir, can you give us details
of this operation?
We've been planning
this for the past few years.
We got the intel that
Masood would be attending
a relative's wedding in London
and that he wanted Mr. Maanav
to perform there.
You mean Bollywood actor Maanav,
who went missing after a murder?
Yes.
But he isn't missing.
He is a true patriot.
He went there because
we had asked him to.
I have an offer for you.
It'll fix everything.
Not the way you want, but my way.
No one will know.
How?
Whether I killed him,
or you killed him.
Or we killed him.
What difference does it make?
It's just a story.
But…
if you add a movie star's name to it,
it'll sell more.
Sir, we do have a lot to gain from this
but will his plan really work?
That guy has killed Masood!
What more do you want him
to do to assure you?
You have 48 hours.
Open negotiation channels
with British Intelligence
and make a list of
what we can offer them.
And, Mohan…
you will bring Maanav back to India.
Play dirty if you have to.
During the shootout at the venue,
Mr. Maanav was of great help to us.
And I'd like to thank
Mr. Maanav for his bravery,
for his support,
and for his contribution to society.
Mr. Sarang will give you
the rest of the details
because he handled the ground assets.
-Sir.
-Please, one by one only!
-Sir!
Sir.
Sir, any police or civilian casualty?
Apart from the casualties
suffered by the UK police,
an Indian citizen named, Bhoora Solanki,
was killed in the shootout.
Let's leave while we're still alive.
I will kill you.
I have a plan.
I have to kill you.
Fine, don't do anything.
Just tell me this,
you know I didn't kill Vicky, right?
The politician in me believed you
on the very first day.
Then what was the problem?
My ego refused to.
Excuse me.
What time will we land in India?
It will be a bright, sunny morning, sir.
Cheers!
All you know is how to win
Twists and turns but you'll never spin
Sorry, sir.
If I don't kill you,
they won't let me go back home.
Action, Maanav.
You don't lose, you never break down
The day has finally dawned
Victory over evil
Get rid of your doubts
Let the wind blow
The war is over
I have the people's support
My hard work has paid off
I will do as I wish
Everyone hated him till yesterday
but now everyone is waiting
for his return.
He is not an action hero,
he is a national hero.
All I'm saying is
that such a drastic change in opinion
makes us look stupid.
Let us observe silence for two minutes.
The good and evil
Going toe-to-toe
Life full of highs and lows
You've made it to the top now
You've got back up, no knockdown
He avenged the bomb blasts.
Learn from him.
The brands that were quick to disappear
are dying to sign Maanav again!
We'd proven him a murderer.
What about Vicky's murder?
Who is Vicky, madam?
He killed Masood!
Now we've made him a hero.
This is the new India, we take revenge.
This man has sacrificed himself
for our nation.
-Maanav!
-Please marry me!
All you know is how to win
Twists and turns but you'll never spin
In this picture of life
You won't get cropped out
Then you learn to
Let loose the fire within
Now it's your time, you got the shine
Your stars align to shoot off
Get away now
You don't lose, you never break down
Every piece fitting into the puzzle
You got it done, you got it done done done
Always ready to hustle